techie-buzz.com 2011-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Techie Buzz

### Techie Buzz respects your privacy

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Techie Buzz.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates.

### Credit card details

Techie Buzz will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you **_Do Not_** enter it on any of the forms on Techie Buzz.

### External Sites

Techie Buzz is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Techie Buzz to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc.). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Techie Buzz does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds.

### Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Third Party Advertising Cookies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Visitor Tracking

Techie Buzz makes use of analytical software such as Google Analytics for statistical purposes. For the purpose of stats your IP (Internet Protocol) Address, browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured. We at Techie Buzz use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

### User Comments

Techie Buzz allows users to comment on the site. However we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion. While commenting on Techie Buzz please refrain from using content that is not suitable.

### Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Techie Buzz and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Techie Buzz have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information please [contact us](http://techie-buzz.com/contact-us/).
